Contact Details

7264818746

shivanitamboli9823@gmail.com

Education

- SSC from Maharashtra state board
 ()
- HSC from Maharashtra state board ()
- B-Tech from SGGSIE&T Nanded ()

Skills

- C
- C++
- Core Java
- Spring Boot
- Hibernate
- AngularJs
- React Js
- AWS
- Jira
- Microservices
- REST API
- SQL
- MongoDB
- Vertica
- Git
- Kafka

Certifications



Shivani Ravikumar Kale

Professional Summary

Quest to work and learn with a progressive organization in which I can contribute my skills & domain expertise, and nurture myself at the same time achieving the organizational objectives with the time, quality, and discipline.

Total Years of Experience

• 4.3 Years

Experience

1. Senior Software Engineer

ErgoTechnology and Services Mumbai

November 2020 - Present

- Significantly contributed to the product to fulfill the customer's requirements using Jira User Stories.
- 2. Associate Software Engineer

Netcore Cloud Solution Mumbai

February 2020 - November 2022

- Developing Methods and solved their queries as per the Client requirement.
- 3. Fellowship Trainee Fullstack Development

Bridgelabz Solutions Pvt Ltd Mumbai

July 2021 - February 2022

- Developing Web Api Methods as per the Models requirement.
- 4. Java Developer Trainee

Tecure Technology Pvt Ltd Pune

Contact Details

7264818746

shivanitamboli9823@gmail.com

Education

- SSC from Maharashtra state board
- HSC from Maharashtra state board
 ()
- B-Tech from SGGSIE&T Nanded ()

Skills

- C
- C++
- Core Java
- Spring Boot
- Hibernate
- AngularJs
- React Js
- AWS
- Jira
- Microservices
- REST API
- SQL
- MongoDB
- Vertica
- Git
- Kafka

Certifications

July 2020 - July 2021

• Developing Web Api Methods as per the Models requirement.

Project Details

1. Paris/Pacos

• Software development with Java Spring boot Domain working on Service and development and Rest.

Technologies Used: Core Java, Spring Boot, React Js, AngularJs, AWS, Kafka, MySQL, DB2, MongoDB

2. Smartech Product

 Software development with Discover Technical Services (SRE Team) working on Development and Service.

Technologies Used: Core Java, Web Api, Spring Boot Framework, React Js, Kafka, Angular Js, Mongo DB, MySQL

3. Book Store App (Copy Of Google keep)

 Book shopping App with Java 8 features, Springboot, Jwt Tokens, JMS Message Queues, Jersey API, JPA.

Technologies Used: Core Java, Web Api, MVC Framework, Angular Js, React Js, Kafka, AWS, MySQL

4. E-learning Platform

• Software development with Java Spring boot Domain working on Service and development.

Technologies Used: Core Java, Web Api, MVC Framework, MySQL